hey what's up everybody Jeremiah Kowski
here what is the best funnel for coaches
to use this is something that a lot of
people ask and they're not quite sure
about because there's so many different
funnel Builders out there there's
different strategies what I want to
bring to you is the best strategy that
we're using right now and actually some
Cutting Edge information that I'm going
to be sharing at the end of this video
as well as some bonus tips if you watch
all the way to the end all about what
will work best for coaches and course
creators and so for those of you that I
haven't met yet my name is Jeremiah
Kowski and for the last 21 years I have
been helping coaches mentors trainers
thought leaders authors scale their
businesses to tens of millions of
dollars in profit online and personally
I've also built multiple coaching
businesses over $10 million a year in
profit so what I want to talk to you
about is what we're doing right now
which is different than what people were
doing even six months ago even 12 months
ago and that's one of the biggest things
to understand is that the way why does
everything change so quickly it might
annoy you that things change and it's
not consistent here's why because human
behavior changes people respond to
different things once one tactic or
strategy gets
overwhelmingly uh used by everybody it
stops working and that's normal as part
of building funnels and marketing your
business and so I get it as a coach and
Mentor you probably crave consistency as
far as that goes that's why getting into
a community like what we have in my
client growth accelerator Community
being able to learn what the cutting Ed
strategies are of what's working right
now as well as plugging into videos like
this on my channel is one of the best
things that you can do to stay up to
speed as to what is working right now
what I'm going to be giving you is the
funnel strategy that we that we've been
using for the last couple of years but
also some of the tweaks that we're going
to be making and changing as well we've
already tested with multiple clients and
seen tremendous results with okay so I'm
going to bring this up on the on the
Whiteboard here the first thing you got
to think about is what is a funnel and
real simply it has nothing to do with
your software has nothing to do with
what platform you use you can use any
piece of software to to funnel people in
basically a funnel is there's people
that are out there and let's say that
this is like in the cloud right here
okay not really a cloud don't you know
don't overanalyze that but let's say
it's raining
leads and a funnel takes these people
and funnels them down
like this into your program okay now not
everybody who is out there is a good fit
for you okay and so the way I look at it
is this is like social media right here
okay and then what you do with your
funnel is you identify and you create
boundaries and barriers on your funnel
like this that's what the walls of this
funnel are to keep out the people that
are probably not going to buy into what
you're doing and they're probably not
going to get results and they're
probably not a good fit and they're not
even part of your niche as far as that
goes okay so the first stage of building
out your funnel is knowing who do you
help who do you serve what sets you
apart as far as that goes then the
number one thing you need to do is you
need to start growing an email list by
marketing to people that are out here
that need solutions to something that
you offer if you are a coach Mentor
trainer course creator
okay then you need to be able to find
the people that need the thing that
you're creating a coaching program
around a course around not everybody is
going to be a good fit for what you
offer maybe you might be a fitness coach
you're like well everybody needs to lose
some weight I get
that but can you hear me out here just
open your mind to the possibility of the
fact that there's actually a smaller
segment of everybody that is far more
likely to become clients of yours than
trying to reach everybody and that you
would have to work 10 hundred even a
thousand times harder to try to just
reach everybody and in fact that's one
of the biggest mistakes people make is
why they don't use a funnel is they
don't want to pigeon hole themselves
into one segment or group of
people that's not good advice that's not
a good idea because you're going to
you're you're not going to be specific
and then when you lack specificity
there's no direction for where people
should go okay and so what you want to
do is you want to direct people to you
for what you offer by attracting them in
this way there's already a ton of people
that need what you have to offer if
you're a coach or course creator okay
there's a ton of people that need what I
have to offer but not everybody who's
out there is a good fit for what I have
to share they're just not case in point
this video we look at the statistics the
people who watch the first 30 seconds of
this video a large portion of those
people don't get to 5 minutes into the
video where you're at right now which
means means that those people are
outside of the segment of people that
I'm looking to reach with a video like
this and you will go crazy trying to
figure out how to capture all those
people and bring them back in that have
left you it's a misappropriated focus
you want to focus on the people that are
drawn into you that are attracted to you
that love you that love to spend time
with you and then you funnel those
people down to find who is the most
qualified for what it is that you offer
okay so you get specific spe ific as to
what you actually are doing with people
and then you move them onto your email
list and then from there you start
providing value to them maybe in the
form of an ebook or in the form of a
webinar or in the form of a vssl or a or
a video content that gets them to listen
to you and build trust with you now
here's what's working best as far as
that goes okay okay what's working best
today and these are the funnels that
we're running right now is if you can
create a piece of video content that's
about 20 minutes long
okay a 20 minute long piece of video
content and by the way this has nothing
to do with your social media or your
YouTube or things like that okay this
can be a Avenue to move people to video
content but actually your content that
you might put on YouTube or social media
is more to build trust what we like to
do is we like to have something that
people have to sign up for with their
email address okay so they have to give
us their email address to get access to
some kind of piece of video content
that's about 20 to 30 minutes long okay
from there you get to tell people about
what you do why they should listen to
you validate yourself to them and show
them what you have to offer then you can
make them a presentation to buy into
something now here's the thing not
everybody's going to buy into that in
fact they're not supposed to off of this
video and that's the key that you got to
understand is you have to realize and
take the long game approach not a long
long game but realize that most people
are too impatient when it comes to their
funnel they are too impatient when it
comes to needing the sale right away on
one first piece of content that they get
understand that that's not not very
practical or realistic because human
beings don't respond that way anymore
and haven't for about the last 15 years
okay and so what you can do and it
doesn't have to take a long period of
time could be within two to three weeks
within two to three weeks they are going
to engage with you with another piece of
content and this could be some form of
content that might be about 90 minutes
long
okay that 90 to 120 minute long piece of
content will be a long form training
where you basically break down the
beginning stages of what you have to
offer in your paid program and what this
does is this is what really seals the
deal so you might get a trickle of
people off of this and you're going to
be and you end up like well why did I
not get more people well the reason why
is you have to build trust with people
more so you Loop people back around to
something that's a little bit longer
like a 90 minute webinar or training and
this closes more people over here of the
people who didn't buy from the 20-minute
training or the 90-minute training they
are still on your email list and then
you get to email them with additional
offers lead magnets ways to build trust
video content that you might put out
there and what will happen is eventually
if you do this and you dial this in with
the right group of people some of them
will become clients of yours and they
will
buy and so if you can follow this
process us and don't over complicate it
keep it simple the goal is this you find
the people you get them on your email
list you provide value in the form of
some sort of live or pre-recorded video
content and you sell to those people
that are on those video content the
thing that you have to deliver to sell
to them again these are things that
require them to put in their name and
email address okay like if you're
watching a YouTube video like this I'm
not making this to sell you anything I'm
not selling you anything this is to make
a connection to teach you to show you to
nurture to build trust as far as that
goes but when I have something that
maybe you have to sign up for with my
email address or I have a live event
that I'm hosting you better believe I'm
going to make a sales presentation and
there's a structure to how we deliver
one of these presentations to be able to
get people to buy into it and so what
I'm going to do is I'm going to actually
give you that structure right now what
we do is we call it the reverse webinar
approach so the reverse webinar approach
is different than most people are doing
their webinars the way that I like to do
it is this is that at the beginning of
the webinar in the first five minutes I
will actually make them an offer about
what I have for sale okay I'm not trying
to keep it till the end so I already get
that out of the way they already know
every single person who engages with me
no matter what piece of content that I
put out there knows that I have
something for sale that I'm offering I
have a group coach coing program that
helps me that where I help people
develop their offers develop their sales
copy put together their advertisements
and I come alongside them to help them
build that with them even in all of my
YouTube content and all of the other
content that I put out there I mention
the offer that I have so there's not a
single person who engages with me that
doesn't know that I have something
absolutely incredible that they can jump
into that will change their life and
their business okay so I don't need to
hard pitch people on that all I do now
CU I get that out of the way first
doesn't that feel really good it
actually feels way more ethical that way
even because you're not there just to
just as a pitchfest just to get people
to buy something okay then what you do
is you actually go into
implementable strategies you go into
actual strategies that people can use
and this will be in your 20 minute
training this can be in your 90minut
training you can even do this in the
format of a 3-day challenge 5-day
challenge things like that okay we still
use those we still use these type of
Live Events to get clients and they work
really really well okay the best way to
get clients as a coach and Mentor is to
get people watching video content that
they had to sign up for with their name
and email address and then even offering
maybe even a paid up sell like a dollar
or $7 on the back end of that from there
then at the end you can go into talking
about your story and this is the really
cool part about this is this creates
safety in the interaction because people
are tired of being pitched they're tired
of just logging onto content and being
sold something they want to know that
you have their best interest in mind so
if you can actually make them the offer
real soft in the beginning and then you
talk about the actual implementable
strategies they know that you're not
just there for their credit card they
know that you actually care about them
and you actually care to deliver to them
what you promised then you can break
down how you got there what your story
is and that creates an emotional
connection to why you can help them as
well and then at the end you do you you
will make a call to action some kind of
action that they can take but you don't
take a lot of time on this you actually
don't have to take a lot of time on it
when you follow this process and this
allows you anytime that you're
interacting with people as a coach or a
mentor you tell them about what you have
for sale real simple confidently excited
about it you tell them exactly what
strategies are going to get them the
result that you promised and then you
tell them your story and loop it right
back to telling them what you had for
sale just real briefly at the very end
that if they want to experience what
you've experienced they can as well okay
so every kind of funnel that you build
is going to follow that process is that
you're going to find people that are out
there on social media let me map this
out for you here real
quick you're going to find people that
are over
on social media and you're going to get
them onto your email list from your
email list you're going to get them to
watch some kind of video content this
funnel is the three stages that works
every single time when it comes to
building coaching businesses selling
courses and reaching the goals that you
have and then the goal of having them
get on the email list do the video
content what's they go through that
video content with you with those three
stages where you do the offer you do the
implementation and you do the story
right here then this leads them
ultimately to purchase from you or if
they didn't purchase from you it Loops
them right back up to your email list
where you can send them another form of
video content pretty simple and this is
the way that people miss it they miss
doing this again I wouldn't recommend
pitching people or selling stuff on your
YouTube or social media content utilize
your YouTube or social media content to
be able to get people on your email list
you're not going to sell to people as
far as that goes I don't have anything
to sell you on this video I have a
waiting list to my coaching program that
I told you about but I'm not using this
to pitch you on it as far as that goes
and in my coaching program we actually
walk you through the whole process of
creating the webinars this way that's
going to actually work for you okay but
once somebody's on your email list you
want them to sign up for some kind of
video training that you get to make an
actual presentation around and the thing
that you really want to grow in is the
confidence to be able to do that the
ability to show up and feel excited
about the fact that somebody signed up
to spend time with you and you want to
create it to where it's engaging where
they want to listen to what you have to
share where you're keeping their
attention and there's a there's a a uh
formula for doing this for keeping
people's attention one of the best ways
to do this is to make sure to mention
maybe there's something at the end that
you're going to share and remember I
mentioned that at the beginning of this
what I want to share at the end of this
with you is that if you follow this
process and the way that we've done in
our business is that we actually get
people onto our email list and each
month we send them some kind of a new
piece of content and it might be similar
to the same one that we sent a few
months ago but we'll put a new spin on
it as far as that goes and we're
constantly getting new clients that way
by being able to retarget people using
Facebook ads Facebook ads that are
retargeted are cheaper than any other
form of advertising and this is one of
the things that I walk all my clients
through is how to set up Facebook ads
the right way if you can run retargeting
ads you don't have to invest as much
money you can invest Le less money up to
95% less money into getting clients in
your business when you run retargeting
ads and that's really one of the coolest
things about the process of R of of
advertising with retargeting ads what a
retargeting ad is this is that if
somebody already got on your email list
the algorithms the social media
algorithms will give you a discount to
show them another ad so because you
already have them on your email list but
maybe they haven't bought yet you can
show them another ad at a discounted
rate and the algorithm will will
actually give you this discount
automatically simply because you got
people on your email list as far as that
goes and so that's one of the best
strategies that we like to use as
coaches and mentors is we' use a
combination of cold marketing with
Facebook ads and with Instagram and with
YouTube and all of this type of stuff by
the way
people always ask which is better paid
or organic I say both you don't want to
just do one or the other I find that
just one or the other doesn't have the
power of doing both together which is
incredibly powerful as far as that goes
and then if you can learn how to get out
of your head where you don't have to
spend hours and hours and hours to think
about what you're actually going to
create content around I didn't take
hours to come up with what this training
was right here I teach this to my
clients every single week I broke it
down simply for you I spent maybe 5
minutes getting into the Zone mental
priming into the right place and now I
showed up on video right here and that's
one of the things that I love to help
people with is they don't have to take
hours and hours and hours to build their
business but they can actually live the
life that they want spend time with
their family and experience Things That
No that most people don't experience in
their businesses and so again if you'd
like to work with me in my accelerator
program I'd love to have you in there to
help you get the results that you want
to help you break through some of the
barriers that are stopping you from
experiencing the kind of success that
you're looking for in your business all
right my name is Jeremiah Kowski make
sure you subscribe and I'll see you on
our next video we'll talk soon